Guide to the Records of the Asian/Pacific/American Institute RG.21.35
New York University Archives
- Series III: Events, 1995-2003
  - Subseries A: General (Alphabetical)
    - Tamiment Library Reception Celebrating First A/P/A Collection at NYU, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Undesirable Elements by Ping Chong, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Vestiges of War Conference, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Vestiges of War Planning, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Where is Home? Conference, 1997 (Box 10b, Folder 1)
    - White House Town Hall Meeting (Box 10b, Folder 2)
    - Who's Next--North Korea and Beyond, 2003 (Box 10b, Folder 3)
    - Wilfredo Lam and the International Avant Garde, 2002 (Box 10b, Folder 4)
    - You Are Being Watched: INS Special Registration and the War on Terrorism, 2003 (Box 10b, Folder 5)
    - Youth Forum on Redistricting (Box 10b, Folder 6)
    - Youth Forum on Redistricting Correspondence (Box 10b, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: Posters, Sketches, and Oversize Materials: A/P/A Events and Activities
    - Asians in America: NYU's First Asian/Asian-American Conference, 1995 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Asians in America: An Interdisciplinary Conference, 1997 (Box Shared University Archives 057, Folder 3)
    - Asians in America: Palates of Pleasure - The Philosophy & Politics of Southeast Asian Food 1 of 2, 2001 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - Asians in America: Palates of Pleasure - The Philosophy & Politics of Southeast Asian Food 2 of 2, 2001 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - Dana Tai Soon Burgess: Reflections in Motion 1 of 2, 2000 (Box Shared University Archives 057, Folder 3)
    - Dana Tai Soon Burgess: Reflections in Motion 1 of 2, 2000 (Box Shared University Archives 057, Folder 3)
    - East of California Conrefence (7th Annual): Rethinking Paradigms, Rethinking Strategies for Asian American Studies, 1997 (Box Shared University Archives 057, Folder 3)
    - Exquisite Crisis & Encounters, 2006-2007 (Box Shared University Archives 057, Folder 3)
    - Faces of Diversity: 27th Annual National Convention, 2005 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - Justice for the Workers: Chinese Staff & Workers' Association Celebrating Twenty Years, Undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - "Man Push Cart" Movie Poster, 2005 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - Maya Lin At NYU - Metropolis Magazine, 1997 October (Box 21)
    - Maya Lin Plans (8 sheets), 1997 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - [Maya Lin?] Large Sketch, Undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - Maya Lin Small Sketch, Circa 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Moving Archipelago: A Century of Writing Filipino America (1 of 2), 2006 (Box Shared University Archives 057, Folder 3)
    - Moving Archipelago: A Century of Writing Filipino America (2 of 2), 2006 (Box Shared University Archives 057, Folder 3)
    - Public Displays of Asiannes: A Conference on Asian American Popular Culture, 1998 (1 of 2) (Box Shared University Archives 057, Folder 3)
    - Public Displays of Asiannes: A Conference on Asian American Popular Culture, 1998 (2 of 2) (Box Shared University Archives 057, Folder 3)
    - Pacifica: New York Hawaiian Film Festival, 2006 (1 of 2) (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - Pacifica: New York Hawaiian Film Festival, 2006 (2 of 2) (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - Still Present Past: Korean Americans and the "Forgotten War" 1 of 2, 2011 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - Still Present Past: Korean Americans and the "Forgotten War" 2 of 2, 2011 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - [Unending] Korean War, The, 1 of 2, 2011 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - [Unending] Korean War, The, 2 of 2, 2011 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - "Up the Yangtze" Movie Poster (1 of 2), 2007 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - "Up the Yangtze" Movie Poster (2 of 2), 2007 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - Vestiges of War 1899-1999: The Philippine American War and Its Aftermath Conference (1 of 2), Circa 1999 (Box Shared University Archives 057, Folder 3)
    - Vestiges of War 1899-1999: The Philippine American War and Its Aftermath Conference (2 of 2), Circa 1999 (Box Shared University Archives 057, Folder 3)
    - Where is Home? A Conference on the Past & Future of Chinese in the Americas, 1997 (Box Shared University Archives 057, Folder 3)
  - Subseries C: General (Chronological)
    - I of Beholder Exhibit, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Assumed Identity Exhibit, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Garden of Export Delights Exhibit, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Coming of Age in Amelika Exhibit, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Spring/Summer 2002 Calendar of Events (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Please Do Not Throw Peanuts at My God Exhibit, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Mind's Desire, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Fall Course Listing, 2002-2004 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Fall Calendar of Events, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - A Photographic Journey with Corky Lee, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Flower Drum Song: Over the Decades, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Spring Course Listing, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Spring Calendar of Events, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - War Retold: Photographs of Vietnam Exhibit, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - An Untold Triumph-Film Screening: Filipino American Soldiers of World War II, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Resident Aliens Exhibit, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Fall Calendar of Events, 2003-2008 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Fall Artist-in-Residence: Fay Chiang, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Fresh Talk Revisited: New York Artists from Fresh Talk/Daring Gazes Exhibit, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - NYU Community of Color Reception, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Through Windows: One woman performance by Susana Lei'ataua, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series: Professor Thuy Linh Tu, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Film Screening: Asian Americans and 9/11, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Screening and Panel Discussion: Matters of Race: The Changing Face of America, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - From Internment and Detention: Abuses Under the Threat of War--Civil Rights Lecture with Dale Minami, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - A/P/A Studies Gallery Exhibition Opening - Fresh Talk Revisited: New York Artists from Fresh Talk/Daring Gazes, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Two Bells, Two Worlds: Film Screening and Discussion, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - A/P/A Studies Gallery Artists Talk--Fresh Talk Revisited: New York Artists from Fresh Talk/Daring Gazes, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - A/P/A Studies 2004 Artist-In-Residence Kickoff Celebration, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Bustin' Through Hollywood: Blue Crush, Bend It Like Beckham, & Better Luck Tomorrow, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Pan Asian Dialogue: Queer Asian/Pacific American Activism, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series with Jasbir Puar, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Chris' Birthday Jam!, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Dissertation Series--Choreographing Chineseness: Global Cities and the Performance of Ethnicity, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Jessica Hagedorn's Dream Jungle: Book Series Launch & Discussion, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series with May Joseph, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Community Health Forum--Walking the Bicultural Tightrope: Psychoanalytic and Literary Perspectives on the New American, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Annual Holiday Party, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Wok Hay: The Breath of a Wok, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - NYU Community of Color Reception, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Spring Course Listings, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Spring Calendar of Events, 2004-2009 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - My Life in Progress by Ian Kim (Student Exhibition), 2004 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Activist Media: Celebrating 35 Years of Independent Film & Video with Third World Newsreel, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - My Life in Progress by Ian Kim (Student Exhibition Opening), 2004 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Impossible Subjects: Illegal Aliens and the Making of Modern America, 1924-1965 (Book Launch & Discussion with Mae Ngai), 2004 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Share & Tell An A/P/A Student Conference, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Lecture & Slide Show Presentation with Anthony W. Lee: "When the Cobbling Began: Photography and Chinese Shoemakers in a 19th Century New England Factory Town", 2004 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Artist Talk with Ian Kim, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series with Jamie Lew, Ph.D.: "Schooling Success and Failure of Korean American Youth in Urban Schools - Significance of Class, Race, & School Context", 2004 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Book Launch & Discussion with Graham Russell Gao Hodges: Anna May Wong: From Laundryman's Daughter to Hollywood Legend, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Queer Asian Pacific Legacy: A Regional Queer Asian/Pacific American Conference, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Disseration Series with Svati Shah, Ph.D. Candidate at Columbia University: "Solicitation, Migration and Daily Wage Labor: Gender, Sexuality and Negotiating Work in an Indian City", 2004 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - 11th Annual Forum on Asian/Pacific American Youth Culture (APAYA), 2004 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - A Most Unlikely Hero: A Documentary on the Fight for Racial Equality in the Marine Corps, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Suburban Sahibs: Three Immigrant Families and Their Passage from India to America (Book Launch & Discussion with S. Mitra Kalita), 2004 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Different Generations/Same Issues: An Evening of Performances Arranged by Fay Chiang, A/P/A Studies Artist-in-Residence, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Diasporic Citizenships: Politics of Belonging for Chinese in Panama: Brown Bag Lunch Series with Lok Siu, Ph.D., 2004 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - At Home in the World: Fictions and Literatures of Asian America and Beyond, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Java House: An Evening of Asian American Performance, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - caucASIANS: Asian Adoptees in White Families: A Discussion on the Transracial Adoption Paradox, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - University Commencement Reception, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - A Dialogue with Separation: Picturing an American Chinatown 1990-2002 Exhibit, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Spring 2005 Events Descriptions (Box 11, Folder 80)
- Series IV: Photographs
  Series IV includes photographs of various events, students, faculty, and staff of the A/P/A Institute and the A/P/A studies program.
  - Photographs: A/P/A Events and Activities, undated (Box 16)
    - Albums
      - Unlabeled -- Album F (2 of 2), Circa 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Unlabeled -- Album F (1 of 2), Circa 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Where is Home? A Conference on the Pat and Future of Chinese in the Americas -- Album E (3 of 3), 1997 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Where is Home? A Conference on the Pat and Future of Chinese in the Americas -- Album E (2 of 3), 1997 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Where is Home? A Conference on the Pat and Future of Chinese in the Americas -- Album E (1 of 3), 1997 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Asians in America -- Album B (Free Zone), Circa 1994-1996 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Asians in America and Other Miscellaneous -- Album D (2 of 2), Circa 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Asians in America and Other Miscellaneous -- Album D (1 of 2), Circa 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Asians in America Confrence and Other Events -- Album C (3 of 3), 1998 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Asians in America -- Album A (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Asians in America Confrence and Other Events -- Album C (1 of 3), 1998 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Asians in America -- Album A (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Asians in America Confrence and Other Events -- Album C (2 of 3), 1998 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Loose Photographs: Labeled
      - AiA, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - EoC, CIrca 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Holiday Party, Circa 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - In Gallery, Circa 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Lowe/Mohanty End of Year Party, Circa 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - PDA Opening and Saturday, Circa 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Do Not Throw Peanuts Exhibit, Circa 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Swati Khurana Exhibit, Circa 1999-2002 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Loose Photographs: Unlabeled
      - Unlabeled Events (1 of 8), Circa 1996-2002 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Unlabeled Events (2 of 8), Circa 1996-2002 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Unlabeled Events (3 of 8), Circa 1996-2002 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Unlabeled Events (4 of 8), Circa 1996-2002 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Unlabeled Events (5 of 8), Circa 1996-2002 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Unlabeled Events (6 of 8), Circa 1996-2002 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Unlabeled Events (7 of 8), Circa 1996-2002 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Unlabeled Events (8 of 8), Circa 1996-2002 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Slides, Negatives, and Contact Sheets
      - Contact Sheets, Circa 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Slides, Circa 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Unlabeled Negatives (1 of 2), Circa 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Unlabeled Negatives (2 of 2), Circa 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - AiA Negatives, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - EoC Negatives, Circa 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - Indonesia Negatives, Circa 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - Lowe/Mohanty End of Year Party, Circa 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - PDA Negatives, Circa 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - PDA and Holiday Party, Circa 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 35)
      - PDA Opening, Circa 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 36)
      - PDA Opening Forum, Circa 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 37)
      - Where is Home, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Series V: Programs
  Series V contains material on the Asian Pacific American Youth Alliance (APAYA), including program activities, surveys, and material pertaining to planning and logistics.
  - Subseries A: APAYA
    Since this subseries contains the records of a youth program, some of the material is restricted because it has recent students' personal and contact information. Folders containing such material have been marked.
    - Logistics: Youth Forum, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Logistics, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Logistics: Pop Culture, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Pop Culture Youth Forum (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - APA Youth Forum, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Introduction Icebreaker, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 9th Annual Forum - Evaluations, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 10th Annual Forum - Evaluations, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - 11th Annual Forum - Evaluations, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Plus/Delta Self Group Evaluations, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - 12th Annual Forum, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - 13th Annual Forum - Evaluations, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Comic Strip - Saturday Training "I am from...", 2002 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Diversity Icebreakers, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Sheelagh's File - APAYA, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - APAYA Resource Binder, 2000-2002 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - 10th Annual Youth Forum Material, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - APAYA, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Planning & Student Release Forms, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - 7th Annual Asian American Youth Identity Forum, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - 6th Annual Asians in America/7th Annual Youth Identity Forum, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - APA Resource Binder, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - APA Resource Binder, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - APA Resource Binder, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - APAYA Forum, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - 5th Annual Asian American Youth Forum (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - 6th Annual APA Youth Forum Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - 8th Annual APA Youth Forum (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - 8th Annual Youth Forum Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - 8th Annual Youth Forum Registration (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - 9th Annual APA Youth Forum (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - 9th Annual APA Youth Forum Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - 9th Annual APA Youth Forum Registration (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Feedback--APAYA, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - 11th Annual APA Youth Alliance Forum Museum Profile, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - "Has APAYA made an impact on you? If at all?", 2003 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - APAYA uncensored, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - APAYA - "APAYA Rules", 2006 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 10th Annual Forum on A/P/A Youth Culture, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - APAYA Makeover, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Human Services for Asian Americans (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Human Services for Asian Americans (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - The Journal of Race & Policy, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - General Information and Training, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - High School Program, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Planning for 2003-2004 Binder, 1 of 2, 2000-2004 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Planning for 2003-2004 Binder, 2 of 2, 2001-2004 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Planning for 2004-2005 Binder, 2001-2005 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Planning for 2007 Binder, 2002-2007 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Workshops, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Forums, 2003-2008 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Series VI: Media
  Series VI contains recordings, in a variety of formats, of various lectures, symposia, and performances sponsored by the Institute.
  - DVCs
    These recordings have been digitized. Please contact the University Archives for access.
    - ACEH Indonesia Conference, RG2135_1 (Box 20)
    - ACEH Indonesia Conference, RG2135_2 (Box 20)
    - ACEH Indonesia Conference, RG2135_3 (Box 20)
    - ACEH Indonesia Conference, RG2135_4 (Box 20)
    - ACEH Indonesia Conference, RG2135_5 (Box 20)
    - ACEH Indonesia Conference, RG2135_6 (Box 20)
    - An Untold Truth, 2003 March 29; RG2135_7 (Box 20)
    - APAYA Forum, RG2315_8 (Box 20)
    - APAYA Forum, 2003; RG2135_9
    - APAYA Open Mic, 2003; RG2135_10 (Box 20)
    - Artist Talk Serene Northington, 2003 February 25; RG2135_11 (Box 20)
    - Assumed Identity, RG2135_12 (Box 20)
    - Catherine Ceniza Choy Empire of Care, 2003 April 8; RG2135_13 (Box 20)
    - Chang Rae Lee, 2000 April 4; RG2135_14 (Box 20)
    - Civil Rights Introductions and Panel 1, 2009 May 21; RG2135_15 (Box 20)
    - Civil Rights Panel 1, 2009 May 21; RG2135_16 (Box 20)
    - Civil Rights Panel 1 Question and Answer, 2009 May 21; RG2135_17 (Box 20)
    - Civil Rights Panel 2, 2009 May 21; RG2135_18 (Box 20)
    - Civil Rights Panel 2, 2009 May 21; RG2135_19 (Box 20)
    - Civil Rights Panel 2, 2009 May 21; RG2135_20 (Box 20)
    - Civil Rights Panel 2 Question and Answer and Panel 3, 2009 May 21; RG2135_21 (Box 20)
    - Civil Rights Panel 3, 2009 May 21; RG2135_22 (Box 20)
    - Civil Rights Panel 3 Question and Answer, 2009 May 21; RG2135_23 (Box 20)
    - Community Health Practical Needs Intro Remarks, 2003 April 12; RG2135_24 (Box 20)
    - Community Health Practical Needs, 2003 April 12; RG2135_25 (Box 20)
    - Community Health Trauma Intro Remarks, 2003 April 12; RG2135_26 (Box 20)
    - Community Health Trauma Forum, 2003 April 12; RG2135_27 (Box 20)
    - Community Health Women and Nation Forum, 2003 April 12; RG2135_28 (Box 20)
    - David Henry Hwang 20 Year Retrospective, 2000 November 14; RG2135_29 (Box 20)
      There is no digital copy available of this DVC.
    - David Henry Hwang 20 Year Retrospective, 2000 November 14; RG2135_30 (Box 20)
    - Elegant Chaos, 1999 February 26; RG2135_31 (Box 20)
    - Elegant Chaos, 1999 February 26; RG2135_32 (Box 20)
    - Elegant Chaos, 1999 February 26; RG2135_33 (Box 20)
    - Fay Chiang A/P/A Air Event, 2003; RG2135_34 (Box 20)
    - Fay Chiang A/P/A Air Event, 2003; RG2135_35 (Box 20)
      Access Restriction
      No digital copy exists of this DVC
    - Felicia Lowe's Carved in Silence, 2002 January 30; RG2135_36 (Box 20)
    - Freezone, 2000 April 8; RG2135_37 (Box 20)
    - Freezone, 2000 April 8; RG2135_38
    - Freezone, 2000 April 8; RG2135_39 (Box 20)
    - Freezone, 2000 April 8; RG2135_40 (Box 20)
    - Freezone, 2000 April 8; RG2135_41 (Box 20)
    - Freezone, 2000 April 8; RG2135_42 (Box 20)
    - Freezone, 2000 April 7; RG2135_43 (Box 20)
    - Freezone, 2000 April 7; RG2135_44 (Box 20)
    - Freezone, 2000 April 7; RG2135_45 (Box 20)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel 1 Intro Remarks, 2002 October 11; RG2135_46 (Box 20)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel 1, 2002 October 11; RG2135_47 (Box 20)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel 1 Discussions, 2002 October 11; RG2135_48 (Box 20)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel 2, 2002 October 11; RG2135_49 (Box 20)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel 2, 2002 October 11; RG2135_50 (Box 20)
    - G. Okihiro Brown Bag, 2003 April 24; RG2135_51 (Box 20)
    - G. Okihiro Brown Bag, 2003 April 24; RG2135_52 (Box 20)
    - Greg Robinson, 2002 March 28; RG2135_53 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Daughters of Taiwan, RG2135_54 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--When You Look At Me What Do You See?, RG2135_55 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Navigating the Next Wave, RG2135_56 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Parachutes Across the Country, RG2135_57 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Juxtapositions Queer Politics, RG2135_58 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--International, Regional, and Local Networks, RG2135_59 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Kazakhstan Adventures, RG2135_60 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Welcome, RG2135_61 (Box 69)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Travelers a Month in NYC, RG2135_62 (Box 69)
    - Jessica Hagedorn Dogeaters Panel, 2001 January 30; RG2135_63 (Box 69)
    - Jessica Hagedorn Dogeaters Panel, 2001 January 30; RG2135_64 (Box 69)
    - Kieng Sen Ong Meet the Artist, 2002 February 7; RG2135_65 (Box 69)
    - Maya Lin and Michael Brenson Dialogue, RG2135_66 (Box 69)
    - Maya Lin and Michael Brenson Dialogue, RG2135_67 (Box 69)
    - Pacific Islands, Atlantic Worlds--Anthropological Engagement, 2001 October 26; RG2135_68 (Box 69)
    - Pacific Islands, Atlantic Worlds--Anthropological Engagement, 2001 October 26; RG2135_69 (Box 69)
    - Pacific Islands, Atlantic Worlds, 2001 October 26; RG2135_70 (Box 69)
    - Pacific Islands, Atlantic Worlds-US Continental Pacific Islander Diaspora, 2001 October 26; RG2135_71 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Opening Night and Southeast Asian Food Panel, 2001 April 19; RG2135_72 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Cultural Presentation, 2001 April 19; RG2135_73 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Cooking Demonstration and Discussion, 2001 April 20; RG2135_74 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Cooking Demonstration and Discussion, 2001 April 20; RG2135_75 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--NYC Appetites, 2001 April 20; RG2135_76 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--NYC Appetites and Food Travels, 2001 April 20; RG2135_77
    - Palates of Pleasure--Food Travels, 2001 April 20; RG2135_78 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Slideshow, Lecture, and Tastings, 2001 April 20; RG2135_79 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Slideshow, Lecture, and Tastings, 2001 April 20; RG2135_80 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Southeast Asian Curries, 2001 April 20; RG2135_81 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Southeast Asian Curries, 2001 April 20; RG2135_82 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Cooking Demonstration, 2001 April 21; RG2135_83 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Cooking Demonstration, 2001 April 21; RG2135_84 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Cooking Demonstration, 2001 April 21; RG2135_85 (Box 69)